Bandi Manindra

→ manindra-004 | in Manindra Bandi | ... +91.7660954555 | w bandimanindramudiraj@gmail.com | → Address: 2-1-461/463 ROYAL VILLA PLAZA, STREET NO 4, Nallakunta, Hyderabad, Telangana, 500044

WORK EXPERIENCE

Designation Nov 2022 - present

I am working on Python/DSA and have also completed basic programming in Java language. Besides that, I also started to learn Web Development as an extra skill and is now a Full Stack Web Developer (Front End + Back End). I don't know that what I am going to do in future but the one thing which I am sure of is that 'I will continue with my coding and work on a skill related to it'.

Designation Mar 2020 - Nov 2022

- Place Organizer and Core Team Member of Google Developer Students Club in my University
- I have done my Internship from Verzeo and worked on MangoDB and Nodejs projects
- In University Projects which was based on AIP Scheduling App for booking slots for teachers and students by the administrator. This project was started in my 4Th semester by inputs from the University administrator about their requirement this project was fully completed 5Th semester ending

PROJECTS

Some Projects Link

I have worked on 3 projects from that recently on MongoDB (Insert Data using form to MongoDB Database create a Database in MongoDB with collection to insert data using form prepare a form using EJS for inserting data to MongoDB)

EDUCATION

2020 - present	Bachelor of Technology (CSE) at NIIT University	(GPA: 6.0/10.0)
2020	Class 12th Telangana Board	(6.0)
2018	Class 10th Telangana Board	(8.4)

SKILLS

Some Skills In Languages- Java/HTML/Python, Design- Adobe XD/Figma/Canvas etc.

Some More Skills EspressJs, Postman API, NodeJs, MongoDB, ReactJs, Microsoft SQL Server, AWS,

Cloud Firebase etc.

SUMMARY

I am interested in learning more new things to get experience that boosts my skills so I wish that I could get an opportunity to work at Goldman Sachs as a Summer analyst/Summer Associate (Internship program)

Last updated: November 28, 2022